Guide to the University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 1845-present UA.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes and Committee Report, April 1868-September 1870 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 6, 1868; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 28, 1868; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 5, 1868; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 4, 1869; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 19, 1869; 5.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees and Committee Report, June 8, 1869; 6.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 4, 1869; 7.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 11, 1870; 8.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 15, 1870; 9.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 4, 1870; 10.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 27, 1870; 11.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 2, 1870; 12.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 28, 1870; 13.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Oaths of Office, 1858-1894 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Roll Sheets, 1863-1871 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 10, 1871 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 16, 1871 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1871-February 1872 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 19, 1871; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 26, 1871; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 27, 1871; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 29, 1872; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 12, 1872; 5.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March-June 7, 1872 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 4, 1872; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 3, 1872; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 7, 1872; 3.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 17, 1872 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 26, 1872-June 16, 1873 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 26, 1872; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 16, 1873; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 23, 1873-February 1874 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 23, 1873; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 27, 1873; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 19, 1874; 3.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1874-November 1875 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 1, 1874; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 8, 1874; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 25, 1874; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 29, 1874; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 7, 1875; 5.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 14, 1875; 6.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 24, 1875; 7.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 30, 1875; 8.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 29, 1875; 9.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1875-June 1877 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 28, 1875; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 5, 1876; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 29, 1876; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 4, 1877; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 28, 1877; 5.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1877-April 2, 1880 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 20, 1877; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 3, 1878; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 11, 1878; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 27, 1878; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 2, 1879; 5.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 26, 1879; 6.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 2, 1880; 7.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, April 30 and June 7, 1880 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 30, 1880; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 7, 1880; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Supplemental Material, June 7, 1880 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1880 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 21, 1880; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 28, 1880; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, July 1880-May 1881 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 22, 1880; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, August 31, 1880; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 12, 1880; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 20, 1881; 4.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 6, 1881 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 21, 1881-April 1882 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 21, 1881; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 7, 1881; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 14, 1882; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 28, 1882; 4.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, May-June 5, 1882 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 9, 1882; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 31, 1882; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 5, 1882; 3.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 16, 1882-June 4, 1883 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 16, 1882; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 29, 1882; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, August 31, 1882; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 30, 1883; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 4, 1883; 5.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 21, 1883 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Bylaws, June 16, 1873 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Articles of Agreement (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, List of Board of Trustees Members and Committees (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Rent Roll, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, General Catalogue, November 10, 1883 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, January-April, 1884 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 16, 1884; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 28, 1884; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 2, 1884 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 19-July 1884 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 19, 1884; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 7, 1884; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1885-May 1889 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 1, 1885; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 18, 1885; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 7, 1886; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 17, 1886; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 6, 1887; 5.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 21, 1887; 6.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 15, 1887; 7.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 4, 1888; 8.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 18, 1888; 9.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 3, 1889; 10.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 28, 1889; 11.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 16, 1889; 12.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 21, 1889; 13.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 3-June 15, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 3, 1889; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 8, 1889; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 15, 1889; 3.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 22-August 1889 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 22, 1889; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 2, 1889; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 30, 1889; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, August 28, 1889; 4.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1889-November 1890 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 24, 1889; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 2, 1890; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 19, 1890; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 15, 1890; 4.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March-June 25, 1891 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 10, 1891; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 17, 1891; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Memoranda and Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 20, 1891; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 11, 1891; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 1, 1891; 5.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 25, 1891; 6.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 27, 1891-June 1893 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 27, 1891; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Memoranda of the Board of Trustees, October 1, 1891; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 9, 1892; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 6, 1892; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 23, 1892; 5.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 29, 1892; 6.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Semi-Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 2, 1893; 7.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 5, 1893; 8.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 22, 1893; 9.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1893-March 1894 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 5, 1893; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 20, 1893; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 19, 1894; 3.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes and Chancellor's Report, June 6 1892, June 1894 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 4, 1894; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 21, 1894; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Chancellor's Report to the Board of Trustees, June 6, 1892; 3.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Roll Sheet for the Board of Trustees, January 16, 1884 and April 12, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1894-March 1895 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 4, 1894; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 27, 1894; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 15, 1895; 3.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 3, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 17 and June 20, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 17, 1895; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 20, 1895; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 3, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March 1896-December 1897 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 12, 1896; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 1, 1896; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 15, 1896; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 8, 1896; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting and Joint Meeting of the Board of Trustees and University Faculties, January 19, 1897; 5.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 8, 1897; 6.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 15, 1897; 7.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 7, 1897; 8.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 17, 1897; 9.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 21, 1897; 10.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March-April 1898 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 16, 1898; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 25, 1898; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1898 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 6, 1898; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 9, 1898; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1898 and May 1899 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 28, 1898; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 18, 1899; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1899 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 5, 1899; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 15, 1899; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 9, 1900; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 4, 1900; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 14, 1900; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 17, 1900; 4.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 10, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1901 and January 1902 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 3, 1901; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 20, 19012; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 27, 1902; 3.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Balance Sheet, June 30, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 2-June 16, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Memorial Minute in Regard to J.D. Thomas, M.D., 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 2, 1902; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 11, 1902; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 16, 1902; 4.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 19, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1902-1903 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 2, 1902; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 5, 1903; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 1, 1903; 3.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 16, 1903; 4.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 8, 1903; 5.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Balance Sheet, June 30, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 3, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 26, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 6, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, School of Mines Groundbreakng Ceremony Program, June 8, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 16, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 13, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 21, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 5, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 12, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 27, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 5, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Reports of Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March-April, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 1, 1906; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 2, 1906; 2.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 20, 1906; 3.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 4, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 49)